{
    "subject": "resource/China",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Renminbi",
    "human_readable": "The currency of China is Renminbi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9811164140701294,
            "question": "Is Renminbi the official currency of China?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9601477980613708,
            "question": "When was the Renminbi introduced as China's currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6643694639205933,
            "question": "What is the currency of China?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6216598153114319,
            "question": "Are there any restrictions on using Renminbi outside of China?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44776153564453125,
            "question": "What is the value of one Renminbi against the US dollar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4041111171245575,
            "question": "Who controls the issuance of Renminbi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4000306725502014,
            "question": "How has the value of the Renminbi changed over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3755128085613251,
            "question": "What other names are used for Renminbi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3726791441440582,
            "question": "How is Renminbi represented symbolically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3236687183380127,
            "question": "What is the role of the Renminbi in international trade?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of China is Renminbi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9122_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Renminbi represented symbolically?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9122_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other names are used for Renminbi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9122_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the value of the Renminbi changed over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9122_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9122_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided support this triple, as the text clearly states that \"Renminbi (RMB) is the official currency of the People's Republic of China\" and that it is also commonly referred to as the Chinese yuan."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that the renminbi (RMB) is the official currency of China, using terms like \"official currency,\" \"Chinese yuan,\" and providing details about its usage and historical context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}